>> 凯尔: 那么让我们看看这四种不同的方法来调用函数。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So let's look at those four
different ways to invoke a function.
我们首先会看到的是隐含的约束力。
The first of them we'll look
at is called implicit binding.
您会注意到我有一个研讨会对象，其中一种方法是这个感知的。
You'll notice I have a workshop object
with a method on it that is this aware.
你应该很眼熟的因为我说
That should look familiar to
you because I called that
我们讨论的另一个单位的名字空间模式
the name space pattern in
another unit of our discussion.
我们在这里重新审视这个名称空间模式
We're revisiting that name
space pattern here and
我们会问这个关键词在那个名称空间模式中是如何运作的 ?
we're gonna ask how does the this key
word behave in that namespace pattern?
当我收到提问时
When I get the ask question invoked,
如何计算此关键字应该指向的内容 ?
how does it figure out what
the this keyword should point at?
问题的答案是呼叫地点的问题。
And the answer is because
of the call site.
由于调用站点，此关键字将结束指向对象
Because of the call site, the this keyword
is gonna end up pointing at the object
它用于调用它，在第 8 行的情况下，是车间对象。
that is used to invoke it, which in this
case on line 8 is the workshop object.
workshop.ask 说，调用会指向研讨会中的此关键字。
workshop.ask says invoke ask with
the this keyword pointing at workshop.
这就是隐含约束规则的含义。
That's what the implicit
binding rule says.
顺便说下，这对你来说应该是直观的，因为这正是
And by the way, that should be intuitive
to you because that's exactly how
此绑定以其他语言工作。
the this binding works in other languages.
所以这个特定规则是最常见最直观的
So this particular rule is the most
common and the most intuitive
因为它是根据你所谓的功能来决定的，我是说，
because it decides the method based upon
what function you call it from, I mean,
你给它起了什么目的
what object you call it from.
但这只是四种方式中的一种
But it's only one of the four ways, and
这才是额外困惑的地方
that's where the extra
confusion can come in.
>> 键盘: 通过该方法，具有隐式绑定的想法很有用，因为
&gt;&gt; Kyle: By the way, the idea of having
implicit binding is useful because
这就是我们在不同情境中共享行为的方式。
this is how we share behavior
among different contexts.
在这里我只定义一个请求函数，但是
Here I am defining just one ask function,
but
我要在两个不同的对象之间分享这个问题的功能。
I'm sharing the ask function
across two different objects.
workshop1 和
workshop1 and
workshop2，两个单独的对象，其中包含两个单独的数据。
workshop2, two separate objects with
two separate pieces of data in them.
但因为在第 7 行和第 12 行，我有对它的要求。
But because on line 7 and line 12 I have
a reference to the ask function on it.
当我使用该引用来调用请求函数时，隐式
When I use that reference to invoke
the ask function, the implicit
绑定规则会在每次不同的上下文中调用该函数。
binding rule says invoke that one function
in a different context each time.
所以我们就没有两个要求的功能，就一个，
So we don't have two ask functions there,
just one, but
它是在两种不同的环境中调用的
it's invoked in two different contexts.
我可以做的不仅仅是 2 次，但我可以做 5 次，
And I could do that not just 2 times,
but I could do it 5 times,
或 1000 次或 100 万次
or 1,000 times, or 1 million times.
在许多不同上下文中使用了一个函数。
One function used in lots
of different contexts.
>> 凯尔: 如果你思考我们如何描述词汇范围的概念，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: If you think back to how we
described the idea of lexical scope,
词法范围的概念是一个非常固定的，可预测的事情。
the idea of lexical scope is a very fixed,
predictable thing.
它是在作者时间定义的，任何关于运行时都无法更改的内容。
It's defined at author time, and nothing
about the run time can ever change that.
在这里我们有一些不固定的东西
And here we have something
which is not fixed and
可预测，它完全是动态的，在运行时完全确定。
predictable, it's entirely dynamic,
it's entirely determined at run time.
这里的交易不是偶然的，这里的交易是很有预谋的，
And the trade off here is not accidental,
the trade off here is very intentional,
我们真正得到的就是
that what we really
are getting is we're getting
可预测和灵活之间的选择。
the choice between predictable and
flexible.
在此，我从能够共享一个功能的灵活性中获益
Here I benefit from the flexibility
of being able to share one function
在不同的环境中
across different contexts.
但有时这种灵活性是负面的，
But there are times when that
flexibility is a downside and
我更希望能有可预测性
what I would prefer is
to have predictability.
不是那个是对的另一个是错的
It's not that one is right and
the other's wrong,
只是这些是不同的工具，有不同的好处。
it's just that these are different
tools and they have different benefits.
在此，我们看到了此关键字的灵活性优势。
Here we're seeing the flexibility
benefit of the this keyword.
>> 凯尔: 还有一种调用函数的方法，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: There's another
way to invoke functions,
我们刚才看到这几张幻灯片的电话方法
we saw this just a couple of slides ago,
the .call method.
.call 方法和它的表弟 .dot apply 方法
The .call method along with it's cousin,
.dot apply method,
它们都将此关键字作为其第一个参数。
both of them take,
as their first argument, a this keyword.
所以在第 13 条，当我们说的时候，我们在 workshop1中通过，
So on line 13, when we say .call and
we pass in workshop1,
它是在此上下文中使用 workshop1 的上下文调用请求函数。
it is saying invoke the ask function
with the this context of workshop1.
与前一张幻灯片很相似，我们仍在共享该功能，
It's very similar to the previous slide,
we are still sharing that function,
但现在我们是明确而不是暗中进行的
but now we're doing so
explicitly rather than implicitly.
我们是说无论这个功能来自何方
We're saying wherever
this function comes from,
请在我要指定的特定上下文中调用该内容。
invoke it in a particular context
which I'm going to specify.
>> 凯尔: 因此，我们可以使用 .call 和
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So we can use .call and
. 适用于显式告知要在哪个上下文中调用该 JavaScript 。
.apply to explicitly tell JavaScript
which context to invoke it in.
现在我们要谈的是明确的约束力
Now, we're gonna talk about
a variation of explicit binding,
这是我们所看到的第二条规则
this is the second of the rules
that we're looking at.
但这不是单独的规则而是一种子规则
But this isn't a separate rule,
but kind of a sub-rule or
此规则的子部分，这是极其常见的场景或
a sub-part of this rule,
which is an extremely common scenario or
称为丢失此绑定的现象。
phenomenon referred to as
losing your this binding.
如果你曾经发挥过你所经历的功能
If you've ever worked with
a function that you pass around, and
突然之间就有了这种束缚
all of a sudden,
it used to have a this binding and
现在它没有这个装束你知道我在说什么
now it doesn't have a this binding,
you know what I'm talking about.
你觉得这个关键词是可以预测的
It's very frustrating when you think of
a this keyword as being predictable and
然后你就会发现，实际上，它是不可预测的，它是灵活的。
then you find out oops, actually,
it's not predictable, it's flexible.
因此，显式绑定的变体称为硬绑定。
So variation of explicit
binding is called hard binding.
查看第 8 行，如果我传入 workshop.ask ，该方法
Looking at line 8,
if I passed in workshop.ask, that method
位于研讨会对象上，但第 8 行不是呼叫站点。
is on the workshop object, but
that line 8 is not the call site.
你要想象在你的脑中，呼叫站点是什么样的
You have to imagine in your head,
what would the call site look like for
当计时器从现在开始运行 10 毫秒时的功能吗 ?
the function whenever that timer
ran ten milliseconds from now?
那个电话站点看起来像 cb[]，或者类似的东西。
And that call site would look like cb[],
or something like that.
这不像是工作员的问题，因为它看起来不像这样，
It's not going to look like workshop.ask,
and because it doesn't look like that,
它不会在工作坊的背景下进行询问
it's not going to invoke
ask in a workshop context.
我们失去了这个束缚我们最终变得没有定义
Which is we've lost our this binding,
we end up getting undefined.
实际上，作为侧面说明，技术上来说，设置超时实用程序
Actually just as side note,
technically, the set timeout utility
是由 HTML 定义的，它不是用缺省的调用来调用的，
is defined by HTML, it's not evoking
it just with the default call,
它在全局的上下文中使用 .call 显式地调用它。
it actually explicitly invokes it with
a .call in the context of global.
所以它实际上是通过 cb.call 窗口来调用 workshop.ask 。
So it would actually invoke workshop.ask
by saying cb.call window, essentially.
在全局对象上下文中调用它，是吗 ?
Invoking it in the global object context,
yes?
>> 演讲者 2: 如果要求我们找到一个箭头函数，那么这是不必要的吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Would this be unnecessary
if ask were to find us an arrow function?
>> 凯尔: 作为箭头函数不能解决问题，但是
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Ask here as an arrow function
would not solve the problem, but
我们会在一分钟内讨论到箭的功能所以我们会回来的
we are gonna talk about arrow functions in
just a moment, so we'll come back that.
所以第 8 行我们失去了这个束缚
So line 8,
we're losing our this binding and
在这种情况下，它会反弹到其他的东西，在这种情况下是全球性的。
it's actually getting rebound to something
else, in this case the global object.
这不是我们想要的
That's not what we want.
因此，一个非常常见的解决方案是第 11 行，传递一个硬约束函数。
So a very common solution to this is
line 11, passing a hard bound function.
如果我们使用 .bind 方法在硬绑定函数中传递，
If we pass in a hard bound
function using the .bind method,
它会把整个柔性的东西拿走
it will take away that
whole flexibility thing and
迫使它仅使用我们在第 11 行上指定的值。
force it to only use the this
that we've specified on line 11.
它说唤起这个功能不管你如何调用它
It says evoke this function, and
no matter how you invoke it,
总是用工作室的方式来做这方面的工作
always use workshop as it's this context.
换句话说，对于 .bind 方法，它不调用函数，
In other words the .bind method,
it doesn't invoke the function,
它产生一个新函数，它与特定特定此上下文绑定。
it produces a new function which is bound
to a particular specific this context.
所以你就在这里做个交易对吧
So you see a trade-off here, right?
您可以看到可预测的，灵活的绑定，但是您会看到一些
You see the predictable, flexible
this binding, but then you see some
在这些场景中， [ SOUND] 令人沮丧的是它是灵活的。
scenarios where, [SOUND] it's kind
of frustrating that it's flexible.
我想说的是超级可预测的
And what I'd really like is for
it to be super predictable.
这里有张力
There's a tension here.
不是说一个是对的，另一个是错的。
It's not to say that one is right and
the other is wrong.
但如果你想在一些问题上做些什么
But if you were to go to all the trouble
to define a bunch of functions on some
名称空间对象，以及
namespace object, and
在每个属性引用和每个方法访问的前面都有这个点。
have this dot in front of every property
reference and every method access.
然后您的所有功能调用都使用 .bind，
And then all of your function
calls use the .bind,
你就会跪下来
you would be cutting
yourself off at the knees.
因为这个制度的整个目的，你交税后的全部原因，
Because the whole purpose of this system,
the whole reason that you pay the tax of
把这个点放在所有东西的前面就能得到炸药
putting this dot in front of
everything is to get the dynamicism.
然后你要把整个动力系统和
And then you're going and
taking that whole dynamic system and
把它锁下来让它完全可以预测
locking it down so
that it's completely predictable.
在那个时候你最好只是写个模块
At that point, wouldn't you be better
served simply writing a module
利用封闭和固定可预测的行为
that uses closure and has a fixed,
predictable behavior?
那么我们如何应对这种紧张局势 ?
So how do we deal with this tension?
我们喜欢用这个关键词对我们有用，但是
We like using the this keyword,
it can be useful to us, but
有时我们需要它不要那么灵活
there are times when we need
it to not be so flexible.
我不能让你紧张
I can't solve that tension for you, but
我可以给你一种我使用的启发式。
I can just give you a sort
of heuristic that I use.
如果我去麻烦写这个代码的集合
If I go to the trouble to write
a this aware set of code, and
那么我的大部分核心位置都是用灵活的动力，
then most of my core sites
are using the flexible dynamism,
每一次我都得做一些很有约束力的事情
and every once in a while I have to
do something like a hard binding.
然后我从那个系统里得到很多好处
Then I'm getting a lot of
benefits out of that system,
似乎是合理的交易
seems like a reasonable trade-off.
另一方面，如果我去找所有麻烦去写这个感知系统
On the other hand, if I go to all the
trouble to write a this aware system and
那么每个人或者我的大部分的电话网站都要不要绑定，这就是我的一条线索。
then everyone or most of my calls sites
have to use not bind, that's a clue to me.
我要硬了
I'm doing this the hard way.
我应该回去用可预测的辞汇
I should switch back and
use the predictable lexical closure.
换句话说，有更好的工具使用，有更好的方法使用工具。
In other words, there's a better tool use,
there's a better way to use the tool.
用它擅长的东西
Use what it's good at.
如果我们想要灵活的活力，请使用这个关键词，如果我们想要的是可预测性，
If we want flexible dynamism, use a this
keyword, if we want predictability,
使用关闭，使用词法作用域。
use closures, use lexical scope.
>> 凯尔: 因此，在使用 .bind 方法时，请记住这一点。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So just keep that in mind
when you're using the .bind method.
不是说不好，不是邪恶，不是反模式。
Not that it is bad, not that it is evil,
not that it is an anti-pattern.
但如果你发现这种情况经常发生
But if you find that happening
more often than not,
你可能是在做苦事
you're probably doing things the hard way.